Vince Gonzalez Data Analyst

Gonzalez.vincente@gmail.com (708) 224-7870 Chicago, IL LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/3mUeyAR
Tableau: https://tabsoft.co/3mRtyQ9
GitHub: https://bit.ly/3kU5DOc

Data analyst with 7+ years of sales and relationship building experience. Ambitious professional skilled in analytical thinking and developing creative solutions. Effective at statistical analysis, crafting presentations using visuals and communicating findings to audiences and platforms ranging from peers to C-level executives and in-person to video conferencing.

Skills		
Python	•	A/B Testing
Data modeling and	•	Storytelling with data
analysis	•	Data Visualization

Recent Projects

Project: First Pitch Analysis

Excel

Tableau SQL

- Analysis of 722,161 pitches from the 2019 MLB Regular Season. Examined outcome probability on the first pitch of an at-bat using Python
- https://bit.ly/338kApR

Project: Fuel Economy Analysis

- Identified four real world concerns on fuel economy, then utilized data to develop insights for consumers
- https://bit.ly/337RXJh

Experience

Fund Conference

Chicago, IL

Enterprise Growth Manager

November 2019 - May 2020

- Identified and built relationships with potential sponsors for FUND Conference events
- Conducted strategic outreach to regional industry leaders
- Researched and developed customized proposals to prospective partners
- Tracked data regarding deal flow to increase conversion rate utilizing HubSpot

ScrapGo Chicago, IL

Regional Account Executive

May 2017 – November 2019

- Effectively communicated and negotiated pricing to buy/sell auto commodities/ferrous and non-ferrous material
- Created sales dashboards in Tableau showcasing monthly price and prospect tracking
- Gathered competitive intel on calls to discover market prices for commodities
- Tracked calls, tasks, opportunity pipeline, mass email metrics and monthly reports using Salesforce

Education

THINKFUL

May 2020 - August 2020

Data Analytics

- Learned how to extract and present actionable insights that deliver business value from common data sources like Excel,
 CSV files and SQL databases
- Practical mastery of Excel, PowerPoint, SQL, Tableau, and Python for data analysis

Morton College

Business Management

Fall 2009 - Spring 2011

Completed Coursework: Principles of Marketing, Principles of Economics, College Algebra